http://www.jamiesonins.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy Because your privacy matters
WE’RE SERIOUS ABOUT YOUR PRIVACY.
We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information that may be collected by us on our site.
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on application or other forms;
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others;
Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency
We do not disclose any nonpublic personal financial information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law.
We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform services on our behalf.
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with state and federal law to guard your nonpublic personal information.
Here to Help
802-496-2080
info@jamiesonins.com
Quick LinksClient Portal
Report a Claim
Request Policy Change
Request Certificate
Request Auto ID Card
Or, Contact Us
About Jamieson Insurance Agency As an independent insurance agency, Jamieson Insurance sells the services of a wide range of insurance companies. Your needs will be carefully reviewed, then matched with the company offering the best protection at the most competitive premium.
Jamieson Insurance Agency, Inc. offers you the advantage of many years of experience in Vermont. Our experienced agents offer personal service, competitive rates and customized programs. Our strength, stability and local knowledge allow us to provide you with quality insurance coverage and service.
Contact us Richmond:
53 Rail Road Street, Richmond, VT 05477
(802) 434-4142
Waitsfield:
5523 Main St, Waitsfield, VT 05673
(802) 496-2080
Waterbury:
© 2020 Jamieson Insurance Agency, Inc. | Vermont Insurance.
All rights reserved. | Privacy Policy
Photo Credit
© Brian Mohr (EmberPhoto) | Powered by Forge3 ActiveAgency.
How can COVID-19 impact your business's insurance?
How can COVID-19 impact your business's insurance?
Read More
Info Center
